当我还是一个在学校的年轻人时，他们告诉我们，我们有五种感官，但我会争辩
When I was a young person at school they taught us that we had five senses, but I would argue
今天他们忽略了一个非常重要的第六感，即平衡感。
today that they have overlooked a very important sixth sense, which is the sense of balance.
对于像人类这样的直立行走动物来说，平衡感是绝对必要的，
The sense of balance is absolutely essential to upright walking animals like human beings,
并且我们使用位于我们内耳，前庭的一些感官来达到平衡
and we achieve balance using some senses that are located in our inner ear, in the vestibular
设备，我们有相当于提供的加速度计和陀螺仪
apparatus where we have the equivalent of accelerometers and gyroscopes that provide
让我们保持正直的信息。平衡绝对是至关重要的，也是人类的第六感。
the information to keep us upright. Balance is absolutely critical and the human being’s sixth sense.
其他动物已经进化出不同的感知
Other animals have evolved different sensing
人类拥有的方式。例如，像蝙蝠这样的小型飞行动物就有这种感觉
modalities to those the humans have. For instance, small flying animals like bats have the sense
回声位置;它们发出声能脉冲并听取反射
of echo location; they send out pulses of acoustic energy and listen for the reflections
他们在晚上以相当高的速度飞行时会使用它来寻找障碍物
and they use this when they are flying at quite high speed at night to find obstacles
他们想要避免并找到他们想吃的昆虫。
that they would want to avoid and to find insects that they would wish to eat.
鲨鱼在身体周围创造一个电场，然后它们可以感知干扰
Sharks create an electric field around their body and then they can sense disturbances
在他们的电场，这是由鱼靠近游泳引起的
in their electric field, which are caused by fish swimming in close proximity to the
鲨鱼的身体，这对他们来说非常有用，以便检测食物的来源。
shark’s body, and this is really useful for them in order to detect sources of food.
最后，鸽子具有天生的磁性感。他们有磁感
Finally, pigeons have got an innate sense of magnetism. They have magnetic senses in
他们的头让他们知道北方在哪里，这绝对是必不可少的
their heads that allow them to tell where north is and this is absolutely essential
对于他们长途飞行，一个必不可少的导航援助。
for them in their flying long distances, an essential navigational aid.
现在对我们来说，几乎不可能想象出“北方”的感觉，
Now for us, it’s almost impossible to imagine what a sense of ‘northness’ feels like,
但是鸽子有这种感觉，因此动物有许多很多不同的感官
but pigeons have that sense, so there are many, many, different senses that animals
随着时间的推移已经发展，以帮助他们履行生活的基本功能。
have evolved over time to help them perform the essential functions of life.